So it's two weeks from prom and you don't have a date.
What are you going to do?
Or maybe you have a job interview for that dream job
and you really want to win the employer over.
But how do you make sure they like you?
Well, there's actually a very simple solution
and it's called not who you want to be.
Not who you want to be turns you almost instantly
into who someone else wants you to be.
For those last minute date fiasco's important job interviews,
awkward meet the families, you name it.
Now, some may say you should always be who you are,
but take it from me, this product can come in handy
in a multitude of situations.
All you have to do to ace that interview,
have the family fall in love with you, or get that date,
is simply program the name of the person you're trying
to impress into the machine and how long you'll be with them.
And out pops a pill and within 20 minutes,
you'll be their favorite person in the world.
This pill carefully works to install a mental filter
for those boys who seem to lack one,
bring the quiet girl out of her shell,
or quiet the incessant talker.
Nothing else can make you so instantly pleasing
to those people you have to impress
for a short period of time.
Not who you want to be is recommended
by four out of 10 marriage counselors
and nine out of 10 mother-in-laws.
Not who you want to be is brought to you
by who would want to be you,
the family company that's brought you such products
as Spanx, Heradai, and Concealer.
Who would want to be you is turning the expertise they possess
and changing your physical exterior
into a fantastic product that can change your personality.
Just like Spanx and Concealer don't actually get rid
of that extra tub you've got,
or that zip you just can't stop thinking about,
not who you want to be doesn't actually change who you are.
However, unlike our other products
that turn your inner beauty outwards,
not who you want to be turns your outer beauty inwards.
After years of laboratory research, careful tests,
and extensive studies, you can be sure
that not who you want to be subtly changes your personality,
but never fails to return you back to normal.
So you can be who you want to be
after you've had your fill of being, not who you want to be.
Not who you want to be is not recommended
for people with multiple personality disorders.
Not who you want to be,
but when you feel like you're just not good enough.
Thank you.